When they will close this age, they come
here to drink coffee and talk to
each other.
He and I told that person that
I'm
at home, it will cost a lot of work.
However, we call it picric FA,
meaning it grows quickly.
Two of my Chinese friends went
shopping in Timor, they planted this tree. The
couple went to buy it, they got stuck
here. We were very happy to hear
that this tree is here.
After digging it up,
from the first year there were those fruits.
50 special things are the heart. Why are
we talking about this? Now let's
go back to text II. Uh, uh, uh, uh,
when almost everything that you and
I tongue together... We do something good
for one day, we will collect
these karmic seeds, and later, abstain from these seeds. It will bloom, we'll see an
Indian movie, and then the
result will be much bigger than a kilogram of seeds.
Someone does something good for
another because the seed
has finished.
Yes, it's a seed.  It's like that practice. A small seed grows
into a large tree, and compared to a white-skinned tree, the
result is that after that tree,
you have to record
another seed naturally, and with a
different mind, it develops on its own. There
is a memory where the golden body blossoms,
creating a lot of sad energy. With a different mind, it
will be read, it will be multiplied,
other vegetables and fruits will bloom and die, like
sugarcane or betel nut trees, peach trees, they give
you fruit. My teaching on
this topic is very beautiful. There is one, yes, yes,
two peaches outside, and one day, I
dedicate it to the child in Nghe An, and one day, after eating, I
throw the box outside.
Now the fruit transforms into seeds, and
it continues to colonize like
that.
Three days, comparing the Bodhi tree, the mind is like
the fruit, eating fruit. In my class, it
never, but it continues and
multiplies, like an
upward spiral. And that's from this to Geneva, I
explain. If you want,
in this class, we  We often say, "
Go away, go away," we say
things like that, Mom. Let me see, you can see the
opposite world, the seed of wisdom. When
you reach the level of an
enlightened person, can you continue and create
support or not? Because karma
always has a little bit of it, that is bad and good. Sometimes
we say it's a little bit good,
but it's dirty, meaning it will wear away and
decay.
After you become a student,
we don't call it support, we call
it two accumulations. Let's analyze
that, merit and wisdom. Day 5. Yes,
what if you want by
accumulating merit? Write the formula, that is
the state, there is nothing better than
Bodhicitta.
Yes, but without Bodhicitta.
And you can make offerings to hundreds of
thousands of people.
And if you can do that for
many thousands of
years, even up
to 100 days, a group of hundreds of thousands of people,
the goods at the planet of all the
precious jewels and offerings.  For
all of you, bidding farewell to people for billions of years, at
some point that good vision will fade away and
you will need to start again.
However, if you are C, meaning
if you do Galaxy A
3, even if you don't practice the six
paramitas, complete after the third year of school, uh, uh, even
if you don't have those
distances, there are sacred moments
in your life. It does
n't happen very often.
For me, once every few months,
there are those sacred moments,
very peaceful, very grateful. He
said that you have times when you are in
a moment where you are eating a
funfly, meaning a bird in Donald's mouth.
Ah,
here is one of the things I
really like, the femen potato dish,
a rooster feeding the bird. This
is what the Buddha often did. The school went to the
hospital to buy potato chips, almost
all of them, and a few pieces on the
bird that was standing outside
Donald's mouth. Today, we have a
special spiritual practice.  Take
some potato chips and
before throwing them to the bird, pray
like this: if you register for
these expenses, you will become one
of my first disciples. When, yes,
when most of the sheep in
our country hold scissors, the technological birds,
and then throw
this piece of potato chip to the bird to eat, and if you
throw this piece of chip to the
little bird, besides the tired Donald with a
moon like that, the Bodhisattva Prayer is
not more powerful than bringing all the
precious jewels on the chest of billions of planets
in conjunction with the year for billions of people,
masks are more powerful than something, it is even more powerful than
karma, and also like meeting a demon.
So why open that martial arts movie, it will
multiply, saying bad things, but more importantly, it
never disappears, people
call it sugarcane because it is a doctor.
Harvest once at the beginning of the year, just continue at
a. The quality of this popular fingerprint is still
it will never end. He goes to
FPT school, there is fruit, it will turn into
seeds, and it just continues.  It multiplies itself like
that, then you will practice the six
paramitas and you will produce news that is
difficult to secret the next sea... uh uh... I
haven't had the experience, it's very difficult to
describe, but I'm telling you all to
try to imagine if the face is
something, but you do something that
affects Ha Tinh. What
would that experience be like on the day
you answered like this? You take
a Kien Giang and give it to someone, whether it's
good or not, that's a
good industry.
Sunday, Monday, it could be karma
and establishing karma so that on Monday it
increases in a lovely way or not,
that's a home now. Try to
imagine, in general, when you have money,
like a Cuong, a quick thing for
someone else, and at the same time
you can make offerings, you can
give to everyone in
one person, the law about the second region, and it
will multiply and accumulate accordingly.
Now, imagine when
you see the level...  Multiplying and doing that for
countless people without a limit, you
can consider yourself capable of doing
that, you will achieve good results. Yes, yes,
Mr. Dai, try it.
After you give one Kien Giang to
one person, the result is
multiplied many times over. Now imagine
in your head, if you were a Bodhisattva and you gave
that natural gift to one person,
it would be equivalent to
giving a gift to a Kim Bang Ha Bodhisattva.
Such an action would be
possible for countless
people and billions of planets.
Can you imagine what that karma would be like?
Take advantage of that good deed.
One person doing it for countless
beings and countless planets.
Just imagine all the statues they give. Imagine
a normal person placing an
incense stick for someone, and that person
is a worker or
a champion. If you do something,
imagine what it would be like to do it for someone. The Vietnamese language is
good, but I
don't know how it would be.  Now you can imagine that x
x + number of particles. Try to imagine a
good experiment, but like it, listening to
music similar to spirituality without bad
particles, without reaching it, without paper, without chairs,
without round chairs,
all the children, because after A,
there are so many universes here. Da Nang,
giving away things like stars, planets
like that, I imagine you just
do one action that affects
countless
beings, you can't compare it to anyone,
no one can compare it.
If an ordinary person can learn to make
rim and achieve that increase, and
what you are doing to help, what if people
can't measure it, can't
compare it to anyone in
this world, it's incomparable. But you
have that experience in 20 minutes, when
you connect with each contestant
on a full scale,
what more amazing thing can you do than that? Uh, uh,
all day I'm saying if you curse, you're cursing,
today is Tet, going to
school, a memory of...  A Bodhisattva, when they
read the Omega mantra diary, wearing a pink hat
like that, it's impossible to count.
When I tried to find a picture to
help you see the infinite number, if it were like that,
this picture would
symbolize infinity. That is, there is no end, no
conclusion, no countable number,
no number that can be
determined. Infinite gift to all of you
listening to this class, all of us, we all want to
become good people,
we all want to do something good for
others.
Sometimes we also have thoughts about
life, but most of
us here want to become
good people, we want to do something to
help others, we do
projects, we determine the meaning of
helping people, those who
have goals, or you have a
third box multiplied by 10, the
excess of the experiment is good, it's just
having that attitude, any of
a person with Bodhicitta who wants to help
all centers, it will have many
results, it's very inexhaustible.  It's incomparable
to something that can
happen. You can come into contact with some of
them on billions of planets and
connect with them and promise to take care of
them. That can happen.
You read that the old woman does good things, and they
are all good things. But if you
have a wish to attain Bodhicitta,
that's incomparable to
others. Others haven't achieved it yet. You
also choose how to cycle for both
Tiki and... and...
Tonight there was a poor person in the
time when Buddha was still alive. I
found these stories: a very
poor person, a woman who said many things about
people with Bodhicitta, offering a
small butter lamp to Buddha. "Bababha, Bababha, Baba," she said, "In
October, this lamp will never go out until I return here and become a Buddha." "Hello, beautiful Ngọc, this lamp will
never go out until I
return here and become a Buddha." "Then
I will return here and
become a Buddha." And we go into
this autumn month. I hope there will be a
retreat that you all can attend.  It's possible to go to
this diamond monastery where
that surgical addict participated in my project when
I came, I was comfortable. I was there
before, so there was a time when I
started coming here, I had to be in
a very expensive hotel.
Now imagine her, yes, yes, she
left this student connection, and
when she left, we once thought like
that, yes, yes, yes, yes.
He was in Germany, and
when that little girl was learning to play the guitar, it was still burning.
This woman said that day, he said, "Come
back now,
because of secret love when harvesting, so that we
can go against the wishes of
our ancestors. There was a time when one lit it,
how to come, then what, Phuc Hoa, I came back
here until my legs were high, came
back here. Hey,
you're learning to swim, this will continue, that's what's
called a new, tiny thing.
Aa33, Thaaj, the temple tower, and then we
left. Go outside. A
game, come back, the
elementary school, the guitar from that butter part,
shining, so I feel the planet.  Uh, yes, yes, I
went in. The next morning it was still
shining, maybe it was keeping everyone
awake. The Buddha told it that on the day of eating chicken,
you can blow out the common cup, but it
will cause a fire.
And you're missing this task, using your sleeve to
blow it out. Hehe, this butter lamp, and
because it can't do that... uh, yes,
the phantom in Korean. There's a
disciple of the Buddha who has a very strong elastic band
and uses his body to blow out
this butter lamp. Buy Garena, make
two devices, listen to the clip
of him successfully using it to blow out this lamp.
Day and night, connected to the heavens, there's a very
high and distant heaven. But this achievement is beyond, outside,
to a place where you can see
the planet,
our planet, where that butter lamp is... uh, yes,
during the day I used the
gas station, the rain
on the planet,
the bank, and a raindrop fell down, a
big one, each drop was so nice.
I made a hose... uh, yes, very much.
Uhuh
A1, the teardrop fell so big? Uh uh, even
grandparents couldn't extinguish that desire,
so the Buddha said, "If you hear about
death, then give up," and then he said, "Uh uh,
when this sweet little lamp is lit
by someone with Bodhicitta, you wo
n't be able to extinguish it.
Forget about it, because nothing
in this world can compare
to the power of Bodhicitta.
Yes, this is wonderful. I'll tell
you all about it. Uh uh,
A, and then the old lady, this table, the person who
cut the lamp these days, oh, the old lady,
you see, you like to learn, the lamp is still
lit.
Our grandparents are so happy, aren't they,
sir?
And then
when the Buddha,
Uh uh, Hey,
you, the Buddha smiled. Uh uh, Uh uh,
Brother, the Buddha smiled. Uh uh,
wife,
Uh, so what does the Buddha's smile look
like in the sutra? Ah,
hi hi, what was the Buddha's reply? He
just smiled.  Smiling Buddha,
what does a smile look like, and do you want to know what
it looks like? Uh, uh, the
bright branch radiates from somewhere. Do
you get blue light,
yellow light, red light
? Are you having a white breakfast?
Comparing
two people, it happens when the Buddha is
immune, that's the end of the story.
In the house, the list of Green Day VTV3, the
common point is also mentioned like that.
If silver has the ability to inspect a
mind that you want to help buy the number of sentient beings, are
you doing this? Uh, uh,
what are you doing? 100 dollars. What are you doing,
sir?
He listens to music
when he's sad. He
doesn't have a meditation pool, he doesn't have
coffee meditation, he doesn't have money for
coffee, he doesn't have it. I
think of the project diary of the fish. She
sleeps like a dead person, and he's injecting
weak energy, a lot of karma because
he has Bodhicitta. Part 5 of the next game is
about if you have someone to care about, no matter what.
You do all day, no matter what you
do, even when...  You sleep, you
accumulate strength, some good advice has
explained it like this: when you
reach Bodhi, you can be like Ngo
Quyen and you can sleep. I like
this promise, and now I even like to sleep,
and if I can accumulate good rest days when
I sleep,
and even the Dharma and the mind watching
Netflix, this is the
best method, the best solution, you should sleep to sleep all
day, and you can still
have the skills to gather
good experiences. You
won't burn out, you know.
When you have a quality, you have skills that have
very good qualities,
even when you sleep, even when
you do things like watching movies,
you diligently produce a
lot of good things. I like that, I
will stop when I get to go because I'm afraid of
liking to sleep,
when that is another conductor of
Mr. Shantideva.
Yes, you said on the day, for
you, counterfeit goods, the legal issues said you
will achieve graduation,
just like you, remember? When I will eat [ __ ].
The principles of becoming a Bodhisattva,
I commit to that. You remember the old days
when we learned about the mind moles? There
are two stages. You can truly
commit them to the Bodhisattva, you just
identify with the idea. I... yes,
yes... to think about becoming invaluable, and
they have been able to achieve
those subtle good signs, that is, sleeping. Watching movies can still be
acceptable, there are many good occasions,
even if you just sleep or watch movies. There are
times when you should watch movies so you can
relax, so add a good movie, don't
watch movies that plant
bad seeds in your head. This point,
this good thing, it is never interrupted.
Now, today, the technical aspect, the
very famous idea of
Shantideva, this is another mother. And
right? The daughter has a
headache, and the mother gives her an
Aspirin and water to take the
pill. The pill is gone,
sir.
All day, even when it ends, nothing
more than getting the pill.  Aspirin in
someone to get rid of their headache, you
still get very good karma. Just such
a simple action,
if you have this intention, you can
imagine encountering the head of
countless beings. Yes, yes,
you will accumulate until the good day, very
rewarding, even if you, my friend,
want to take away this person's headache.
You only have one process. If
you happen to have someone take away the
suffering of countless beings,
you can imagine how many
good deeds you accumulate.
How can I tell you?
Yes, from the 5th of the month, you have to thank the movie.
I mean, go on Thursday, class 5, yes, yes,
35, a chair of tomato sauce on
Fantasy.
Are you writing in the middle of the sun, saving
its temperature, it's about very high, the
temperature is really high. I will continue
this topic about how powerful the Bodhicitta is
and  How is it possible to eliminate
negative karmic contamination
when this is what is so appealing about Mr.
Shantideva? If you prepare
a meal, it
will take me three or four hours to
cook a meal, and you can
eat it in 15 minutes. If
I prepare a delicious meal, it takes me three or four
hours, but if you prepare a meal
for a certain day and you're not skillful, you
make a mess. When you
make snacks, it's not very enjoyable,
sir.
Even if you cook for a
certain day and you're not happy cooking for
a certain day, to eat until you're full,
people still say to you, "Sir, it
's a very good deed." Suppose you
make a meal for countless beings
and you never want to eat it, it doesn't
hurt their stomachs. Then that meal will bring them
hope and dreams forever,
sir.
Yes, the point that Mr. Shantideva wants to make
here is when serving the cook in
Someone for business meeting, welcoming
Mr. Khanh, good student, I really like
cooking for others.
Yes, for business, someone and cooking for
them, making everyone happy, hot
food for my mother, just for them to eat. It's a
delicious meal for them, it makes everyone
very happy.
You can imagine that,
that thing, for countless numbers, and they
go to a number, a number zero, put together,
and we will see. So this last time,
we will stop here when your
husband cooks a meal from natural land, you
a land, and this land will
never stop. Oh,
he goes to this land, it will never stop
working.
This land will not say, "I
said, my husband, I don't want my
husband anymore, I don't want to work to
create exams, the organic matter
will continue to work for you
forever. If you don't have ovulation,
it will continue to create crops for
you forever, without stopping." Yes, yes. Oh,
usually in a little India, taking care of
it just  Yes, that's right, the electrocardiogram machine is
like a field that
never stops working to produce
crops for you.